http://www.thepeoples.com/privacy-policy

Skip Navigation Documents in Portable Document Format (PDF) require Adobe Acrobat Reader 5.0 or higher to view,download Adobe® Acrobat Reader.
FACTS
What does The Peoples Bank do with your Personal Information
Why?
Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.
What?
The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:
Social Security number
Account balances and payment history
Transaction or loss history
Credit history and overdraft history
When you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.
How?
All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons The Peoples Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing.
Reasons we can share your personal information
Does The Peoples Bank share?
Can you limit this sharing?
For our everyday business purposes -such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureaus
Yes
No
For our marketing purposes -to offer our products and services to you
No
We don't share
For joint marketing with other financial companies
No
We don't share
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -information about your transactions and experiences
No
We don't share
For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -information about your creditworthiness
No
We don't share
For nonaffiliates to market to you
No
We don't share
Questions?
Call 228-435-5511
What We Do
How does The Peoples Bank protect my personal information?
To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.
How does The Peoples Bank collect my personal information?
We collect your personal information, for example, when you
Open an account or withdraw money
Apply for a loan
Show your government-issued ID or use your debit card
Why can't I limit all sharing?
Federal law gives you the right to limit only
sharing for affiliates’ everyday business purposes—information about your creditworthiness
affiliates from using your information to market to you
sharing for non-affiliates to market to you
State laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing.
Definitions
Affiliates
Companies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
The Peoples Bank has no affiliates.
Non-affiliates
Companies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and non-financial companies.
The Peoples Bank does share with non-affiliates.
Joint Marketing
A formal agreement between non-affiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.
The Peoples Bank does not jointly market with other companies.
Other Important Information
The Peoples Bank believes your privacy should not be compromised, and we maintain standards to insure that your information is private and secure at all times.
